# Gabriel Almeida

São Paulo, São Paulo, Brazil

gab.galmeida@outlook.com

+55 11956815510

linkedin.com/in/ggalmeida

# **Summary**

I am an experienced professional, working in the IT area since 2006. I am very committed in all areas of my life, and am always setting up and achieving new goals both professionally and personally. I work hard and I strive to be the best in everything I do. I have excellent communication skills in English, Spanish and Portuguese languages and work well in an international environment. I work without supervision, am dependable and honest and am respected by my peers.

# **Experience**

# **Software Developer**

CI&T

Aug 2021 - Present (7 months +)

- Designed and implemented a CI/CD Pipeline from scratch. This strategy with the tools allowed the company to provide training for 30+ developer interns at the same time with minimum overhead for the technical staff:
- Automated Environment Setup decreasing the original 2-day setup for less than 8 minutes;
- Created and implemented management metrics and KPIs raising the team's performance in 182,9% within 90 days;
- Coached and mentored 7 junior employees (directly) and over 40 indirectly, developing their soft and hard skills and preparing them for their next level in career.

#### **Full Stack Developer**

Feb 2019 - Aug 2021 (2 years 7 months)

- Developed WebApps, PWA's, Websites, small plugins and APIs for local customers. Built and maintained an IoT product in a health tech startup developed in ReactJS/TypeScript and NodeJS/MvSQL.
- Coordinated Development projects with a team of 3-5 developers. Raised the NPS score from 55% to 86%



## **Senior Delivery Specialist**

**Dell EMC** 

Jun 2018 - Feb 2020 (1 year 9 months)

- FrontEnd release planning to perform SRDF connections for migration;
- Planning to define the number of Remote Adapters to perform the migration;
- Definition of standards for creating the RDF Group;
- Replication configuration in SRDF 3 Sites (Cascaded / Concurrent);
- Planning and supporting the use of DWDM as a link technology for migration;
- Planning and support to carry out traffic rebalance in FAs and RAs during the project;
- Training of third parties to carry out migrations;
- Performance report and capacity of the stores involved;
- Participation in the definition of connectivity map for new storages acquired;

- Participation in technical definition meetings for the migration process;
- Support the PMO team in decision making;
- Support in the physical layout and assembly of EMC<sup>2</sup>/Brocade and Cisco equipment in a new Data Center:
- Support in opening GMUDs with the areas involved;
- Monitoring and assistance in the execution of incidents related to fiber part, RGD cables, GBICs and VMAX director and other EMC² equipment;

Implementation of call home and automatic opening service with EMC2;

- Troubleshooting;
- Support to architects to apply all logical configurations and post-implementation execution of switches (initial configuration of equipment, implementation of fabrics, configuration referring to ISLs, LSAN);
- Monitoring of SWs through CMCNE (Brocade Network Advisor).
- Monitoring and configuration of SWs through DCNM (Cisco Switches)

## **Education**



#### **FIAP**

Bachelor's degree, Computer Software Engineering 2019 - 2022

## **Skills**

JavaScript • Drupal • PHP • High Availability • Project Management • Responsive Web Design • React.js • Node.js • Next.js • Laravel